Guide to the International Platform Association records, 1904-2001 MS2273
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual materials, 1977-1999; 1990-1999; Series 7; 23 Linear Feet
  - 1987 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by John Burns, Peter Bensinger, William Colby, Sarah Brady, George Feifer, Allan Lichtman, Cyril Brickfield, David Harper, Claude Pepper, and Yakov Smirnoff.
  - 1987 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jack Anderson, William Brown, Sarah Brady, James Boren, George Feifer, and William Colby.
  - 1987 - 450, 470, 510, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Yakov Smirnoff and Claude Pepper.
  - 1988 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Larry King, Claude Pepper, Stansfield Turner, Brooke Knapp, J. Peter Grace, Vicki Valentine, Sunny, Schlenger, Shirley Chisholm, Wayne F. Nelson, John McLaughlin, and Robert Dole.
  - 1988 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Arnaud deBorchgrave, Michael DeBakey, Cornelius Heine, Nanette Fabray, and Charles Inlander.
  - 1988 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Richard Secord, Philip Stern, Robert Swan, Jonathan Kozol, Jeremiah Denton, George Anne Geyer, Malcolm Forbes, Jr., John Roach, Jack Lalanne, Richard Gillespie, Bill Schustik, and Lorna Kelly.
  - 1988 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Joel Kurtzman, Emmanual Pelaez, John Block, Murray Banks, Terry Eastland, Bill McLinn, Gerry Tausch, Edwin Meese, Joe Clark, Bill Plante, John Cater Brown, and Archibald Roosevelt.
  - 1988 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Rodger McFarlane, Claude Pepper, Peter Mroczk, George Velliotes, Eugeney Kutovoy, Waheed S. Al-'Araby, and Sid Davis.
  - 1988 Convention VI, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Cornelius Heine, Nanette Fabray, Arnaud deBorchgrave, Sid Davis, Waheed Al'Araby, and Eugeney Kutovoy.
  - 1988 Convention VII, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 7)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by George Velliotes, Peter Mroczyk, Claude Pepper, David Harper, Arthur Fleming, Terry Eastland, and Joel Kurtzman.
  - 1988 Convention VIII, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 8)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jeremiah Denton, Georgie Anne Geyer, Michael DeBakey, George Crile, Clause Pepper, John Burns, Peter Bensinger, Jack Anderson, and Richard Secord.
  - 1988 Convention IX, Series 7 (Box 70, Case 9)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Robin Winks, William Roper, George McGovern, Jan Scruggs, Lou Dobbs, Marianna Thomas, Barbara Chase-Riboud, and Jim McGee.
  - 1989 Convention, 011-180, Series 7 (Box 71, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Myrna Williamson, Eleanor Clift, Norman Vincent Peale, Karen Feld, Ken Adelman, Andrew Simmons, Gerry Tausch, Peter Holmes, Frank Capiello, and Milan Svec.
  - 1989 Convention, 160-310, Series 7 (Box 71, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Peter Holmes, Milan Svec, John Dancy, Tom Logsdon, Frank Capiello, Edwin Meese, Allen Sinai, Albert Shanker, Malcolm Forbes, Jim Oakley, Phil Sokolof, Henry Heimlich, David Zach, and Ben Wattenberg.
  - 1989 Convention, 320-460, Series 7 (Box 71, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Alexandra Costa, Pamela Cressey, Pauline Hatch, Alice Fulton, Joan Benny, Bob Arnot, Tweed Roosevelt, Jerzy Jaskiernia, Evan Kemp, Philip Strax, Fulang Lo, Don North, Celeste Holm, and Karen Payne.
  - 1990 Convention, 011-100, Series 7 (Box 71, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Cornelius Heine, Jack Kevorkian, Alice Weston, Gerry Tausch, Alan Keyes, and Taffy McCallum.
  - 1990 Convention, Series 7 (Box 71, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Alice Weston, Gerry Tausch, Cornelius Heine, Alan Keyes, Jack Kevorkian, Taffy McCallum, Pat Paulsen, Keith Blume, Jayne Meadows, and Dumisani Kumalo.
  - 1990 Convention, 110-200, Series 7 (Box 72, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Paul Paulsen, Jayne Meadows, Mario Buatta, Keith Blume, Dumisani Kumalo, Hope Mihalap, Zhu Qizhen, James Mahoney, Mitchell Davis, and Joe Shafran.
  - 1990 Convention, 200-270, Series 7 (Box 72, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Mitchell Davis, Joe Shafran, Tom Logsdon, William Seidman, Jan Scruggs, Susan Willens, Steven Schlosstein, and Jerry and Sis Levin.
  - 1990 Convention, 250-360, Series 7 (Box 72, Case 3)
  - 1990 Convention, 370-460, Series 7 (Box 72, Case 4)
  - 1990 Convention, 470-550, Series 7 (Box 72, Case 5)
  - 1991 Convention, 011-090, Series 7 (Box 73, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Tom Watson, Peter Arnett, Norman Glickman, Lillian Brown, Geri Jewell, and Sheilah Kast.
  - 1991 Convention, 100-250, Series 7 (Box 73, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Don Cruze, Bob Leiman, Alan Keyes, Michael Robinson, Frank Popper, Donald Lambro, Arnold McKinnon, Jim Davidson, J. Peter Grace, Sydney Huff, Gordon Webb, and David Essel.
  - 1991 Convention, 260-400, Series 7 (Box 73, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jim Turner, Studs Terkel, Dale Van Atta, Susan Eisenhower, Cathy Rigby, Carol Willoughby, Doug Stephan, Carolyn Clancy, Myrna Williamson, Cynthia Pricwe Cohen, and Jeffrey Joseph.
  - 1991 Convention, 410-510, Series 7 (Box 73, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Nadine Strossen, Jim Gossett, Mary Beal, Robert Brown, Jack Anderon, Jesse Jackson, Alvin Braff, Ida Stewart, Betty Bao Lord, and Denis McLean.
  - 1991 Convention, Series 7 (Box 74, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Hope Mihalap, Frank Popper, William Proxmire, Carol Willoughby, Bernadine Healy, Jim Davidson, David Musto, Doug Stephan, Dick Cheney, Jeff MacInnis, Jeffrey Jopseph, Jim Gossett, Myrna Williamson, Cynthis Price Cohen, Robert Brown, and Mary Beal.
  - 1992 Convention, 010-170, Series 7 (Box 74, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Eugene Lang, Harry Blackstone, Jr., Gerry Tausch, Myrna Williamson, Jack Anderson, Mikki Williams, Henry Heimlich, Caldwell Esselstyn, Lawrence Kutner, Tweed Roosevelt, Arun Gandhi, Doug Marlette, G. Gordon Liddy, and David Werner.
  - 1992 Convention, 190-350, Series 7 (Box 74, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Wesley Smith, Delmis Wood, Laura Pedersen, Robert Remini, Sarah McClendon, John Esposito, Edmund Haislmaier, John Frohnmayer, Peter Burtchell, John Makay, Patricia Ireland, and Ethel Sexton.
  - 1992 Convention, 360-520, Series 7 (Box 74, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Philippe Villers, A.J. Bradbury, Steve Symms, Eve Capello, Daniel White, Catherine Crier, Micheal Creedon, Antonia Novello, Grover Norquist, Carol Walker, Bob Leiman, C. Barry McCarty, Michael Lewis, and Nanette Fabray.
  - 1993 Convention, 11-160, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Helga Sanburg, Jack Anderson, John Edward Hasse, Joe Cobb, John D. Jacobson, Eli Bay, Alice Tepper-Marlin, David Perlman, Tweed Roosevelt, and Hal Huggins.
  - 1993 Convention, 170-340, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Reed Irvine, Seiichi Kondo, Bob Beckel, Paul Tucker, Anita Hill, Vindo Sahgal, Barbara Hannah Marks, Ross Perot, Joan Matterson, Frank Baranowski, H. Skip Weitzen, Gerry Tausch, Bob Lukefahr, John Brown, Phyllis George Brown, and Martin Gross.
  - 1993 Convention, 350-390, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Peter W. Huber, Joseph Jacobs, Tim Stivers, and Jackie Nink Pflug.
  - 1993 Convention, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Helga Sanburg, Jack Anderson, John Edward Hasse, David Perlman, Tweed Roosevelt, John Jacobson, Eli Bay, Alice Tepper, Reed Irvine, Hal Huggins, Paul Tucker, and Anita Hill.
  - 1994 Convention, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Paul Murphy, Aram Bakshian, Jr., Gilbert Davis, Tom Logsdon, Ruth Stafford Peale, Tweed Roosevelt, Richard Lederer, Myrna Williamson, and Eugene Lehrmann.
  - 1994 Convention, 230-440, Series 7 (Box 75, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Dan Stein, Jeffrey Joseph, Bob Murphey, Lester Brown, Ruby Petersen Unger, Anne Meager Northrup, Thomas Bagley-White, Martin Hoke, Albert Gamper, Hazel O'Leary, Rita Dove, Norma Langham, Martha Phillips, George Martin, Frederick Antil, and Neil Simon.
  - IPA Audiocassettes, 0001-0440, 1994; Series 7 (Box 76, Case 1)
  - IPA 1994, Monologue - NFS, Series 7 (Box 76, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Virginia Pate Hayes.
  - [IPA Audiocassettes], 1994; Series 7 (Box 76, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Laura Bobrow, Virginia Pate Hayes, Jack Anderson, Joycelyn Elders, and Ted Zalewski.
  - 1995 Convention (NFS), Series 7 (Box 77, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Mary Sue Best, David Best, and Nancy Samalin.
  - 1995 Convention (10-170), Series 7 (Box 77, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jack Anderson, Bill Butterworth, Daniel Webster, Jennifer Harbury, John Fund, Gerry Tausch, Horace Deets, Jerry Land, and Mike Harper.
  - 1995 Convention (180-350), Series 7 (Box 77, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Wayne LaPierre, Malcolm Forbes, Jr., Chris Ullman, Tom Barrett, Kenneth Blanchard, William Young, Bob Leiman, Louis Stokes, Dmitry Mikheyev, Don Torgersen, Margaret Warner, Armstrong Williams, Mark Chassin, James Lovell, Robert Hass, and Juan Williams.
  - 1995 Convention (360-462, NFS), Series 7 (Box 77, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Bruce Vogel, Lori Lacey, Donna DeVarona, Carlos Romero-Barcelo, Bob Leiman, Christopher Wright, Charles Osgood, Frederick Antil, Lloyd Ogilive, and John Shalikashvili.
  - 1996 Convention (NFS3-NF59), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Cynthia Maddox, John Makay, Theo Colborn, and Zev Kedem.
  - 1996 Convention (500-560), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Ronald Goldfarb, Jack Anderson, and Delmas Wood.
  - 1996 Convention (570-650), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by William Young, Arianna Huffington, Jane Alexander, Bill Press, Henry Heimlich, Arthur Caliandro, and Robert W. Sweet.
  - 1996 Convention (660-730), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Linda Chavez-Thompson, Donald Lambro, Ralph Reed, W. Wayne Allen, Sam Horn, Robert Bergman, Thomas Schatz, and Dan Stein.
  - 1996 Convention (740-840), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Susan Nichols, Balint Vazsonyi, Kellyanne Fitzpatrick, Kelly Riddle, and Eugene Fluckey.
  - 1996 Convention (850-920, NFS1, NFS2), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Lisa Nelson, Mikki Williams, Bob Bernstein, Shirley Duncan, and Henry Foster.
  - 1996 Convention (500-910), Series 7 (Box 78, Case 7)
  - 1997 Convention (1000-1060), Series 7 (Box 79, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Christiane Amanpour, Richard Behar, Jack Anderson, John Meyer, and James Gordon.
  - 1997 Convention (1070-1140), Series 7 (Box 79, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Margaret Dixon, Bill Butterworth, Richard Cheatham, Charlie Bell, Catherine French, Harry Wu, Jack Butcher, Jack Risin, and James Manley.
  - 1997 Convention (1150-1310), Series 7 (Box 79, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jim Oakley, Ira Magaziner, Joe Sills, M. Stanton Evans, Millard Fuller, Shelley Davis, Mary Schiavo, Bill McKibben, Eve Capello, Dick Morris, David Best, Robert Woodson, Michael Robinson, and John Seiler.
  - 1997 Convention (1320-1350), Series 7 (Box 79, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Elizabeth Drew, Anita Perez Ferguson, Richard Berendzen, and Robert Gallo.
  - 1998 Convention, Series 7 (Box 79, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Michael Farris, Geraldine Brooks, Balint Vazsonyi, Robert Dove, Stanley Spielman, Robert Sims, Jim Laver, S. Truett Cathy, Dorothy Donaldson, Javier Alarcon, and Hal Bruno.
  - IPA Audiocassettes 1997 - 1200 and 1210, Series 7 (Box 79, Case 6)
  - IPA Audiocassettes 1999 - 0020-0150, Series 7 (Box 79, Case 7)
  - IPA Audiocassettes 1999, 0160-0250, Series 7 (Box 79, Case 8)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 1)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 2)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 3)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 4)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 5)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 6)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 7)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 8)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 9)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 10)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 11)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 12)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 13)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 14)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 15)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 16)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 17)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 18)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 19)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 20)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 21)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 22)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 23)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 24)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 25)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 26)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 27)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 28)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 29)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 30)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 31)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 32)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 33)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 34)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 35)
  - 1991 International Platform Association Convention, Series 7 (Box 80, Videocassette 36)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 1)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 2)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 3)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 4)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 5)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 6)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 7)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 8)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 9)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 10)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 11)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 12)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 13)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 14)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 15)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 16)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 17)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 18)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 19)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 20)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 21)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 22)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 23)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 24)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 25)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 26)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 27)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 28)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 29)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 30)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 31)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 32)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 33)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 34)
  - [1991-1993 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 81, Videocassette 35)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 1)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 2)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 3)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 4)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 5)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 6)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 7)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 8)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 9)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 10)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 11)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 12)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 13)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 14)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 15)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 16)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 17)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 18)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 19)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 20)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 21)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 22)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 23)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 24)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 25)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 26)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 27)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 28)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 29)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 30)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 31)
  - [1993-1994 International Platform Association Conventions], Series 7 (Box 82, Videocassette 32)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 1)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 2)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 3)